(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive English -Promise-
2nd Anniversary Concert: Promise 2 You
Ready Steady
Lyrics/Music: Giga
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Tearing through the asphalt as tires screech,
暗闇 走り抜ける
Running through the darkness.
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I surrender myself to cheap thrills,
明日に怯えていたよ
I was afraid of tomorrow.
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone's sake,
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何も怖くはない
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding onto a puzzle of love I can't solve alone.
Get wild and tough
この街でやさしさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to rely on this city's kindness.
Get chance and luck
君だけが守れるものがどこかにあるさ
Somewhere there is something only you can protect.
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも傷ついた夢を取り戻すよ
Even alone, I'll reclaim my wounded dreams.
ありきたりな僕の日々を 壊してくれ
Please destroy these common days of mine
異常なほどの刺激を
I must have been waiting for the stimulation
待ち望んでいたのかな
of something abnormal
ちょっとしたそんな冒険心は
That tiny bit of adventurousness
改札に吸い込まれて
got sucked into the ticket gate
吐き出され辿り着いた
After being spit back out I arrived
雨降るこの街
in this rainy city
何も感じれないまま
I ain't gonna die
死んでいくのはごめんだ
having never felt anything
終わりのその先をめざして
So I'll set my sights beyond the end
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなまま
We're still so uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shine, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Fight back, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
We're amid the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ So there's no looking back
We're chasing after it, so there's no looking back
まだ首を突っ込んで
Still sticking our necks in
見事に散らかしてんだ
making a brilliant mess of it all
あいまいな退屈な
With those vague and boring
気持ちとさらばさ
feelings, it's farewell
関係ないって顔したって
Even if you act like it's none of your business
どこかで繋がっていて
it's connected somewhere
何度だって引き戻すと
Pulling you back again and again
手招くこの街
this city beckons
ピリピリ痺れるような
I want to live right now
今を生きていたいんだ
like I'm tingling with excitement
極限のギリギリで行こうぜ
Let's go to the absolute limit
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなまま
We're still so uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shine, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Fight back, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
We're amid the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ So there's no looking back
We're chasing after it, so there's no looking back
Inside outside just wanna feel good everyday
Inside outside I just wanna feel alive
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Dash out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなまま
We're still so uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shine, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Fight back, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
We're amid the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ So there's no looking back
We're chasing after it, so there's no looking back
Don't take your love away
You ain't heard nothin' yet
Wake up wake up bang
また慣れ出した表情は
That expression I've started to get used to again
あなた今忙しいの
Are you busy right now?
未読の毒と愛顧もいっぱいで
Full of unread poison and favoritism
忙しない 邪魔をしないで頂戴
It's restless, so please don't disturb me
「対等にね」くれた可愛い「イエス」
The cute "yes" you gave me "equally"
内性律 こんなんですか
Is this how the internal law works?
…まだ未練があるのね
...You still have lingering regrets, don't you?
本音は言わないほうが悩ましい
It's more seductive if you don't tell the truth.
甘い言葉かけるよりもずっと愛おしい
Much more precious than whispering sweet words.
たまらなくなるほど 求めて離さないで
Desire me so much you can't stand it, and don't let go.
キスじゃ足りなくて いっそ殺して
A kiss isn't enough, just kill me instead.
Predilection あなたを手にかけて
Predilection, laying my hands on you,
Infatuation 呼吸さえ止めて
Infatuation, even stopping my breath.
Dedication このまま Addiction
Dedication, just like this, Addiction,
して まだたった一口で仕舞い
and with just one taste, it's over.
Predilection さあさ口をつけて
Predilection, come on, put it to your lips,
Infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuation, swallow it as it is.
Dedication すぐさま Addiction
Dedication, immediately Addiction,
して ほらたった一口 死ぬほど愛したいだけ
look, just one taste, I just want to love you to death.
狂ったほどの愛情過多でいい
It's fine to have a madly excessive love.
あなたには私しかいない
I'm the only one you have.
腐ったほどの愛情が足りない
There's not enough of this rotten love.
私にはあなたしかいないなんて
Saying that you're the only one I have.
運命を悟った この手掴んだ
I realized our fate, and grabbed this hand.
まだ未練があるのね また我儘
You still have regrets, and you're being selfish again.
愛と名付けてまた支配する
Naming it love, I'll dominate you again.
あなたに溺れてく 息苦しいくらいに
I'm drowning in you, to the point of suffocation.
侵食させて いっそ壊して
Let it erode me, just break me instead.
Predilection 私を手にかけて
Predilection, laying your hands on me,
Infatuation キスで口塞いで
Infatuation, blocking my mouth with a kiss.
Dedication まだまだ Addiction
Dedication, more and more Addiction,
して まだたった一言で溺愛
and with just one word, doting love.
Predilection 覗く眼差し込んで
Predilection, with a piercing gaze,
Infatuation 躊躇いなど捨てて
Infatuation, cast aside all hesitation.
Dedication すぐさま Addiction
Dedication, immediately Addiction,
して ほらたった一口 これで終わらせないで
look, just one taste, don't let it end with this.
Alas, alas, continue it further
evolve more, my love, my love
is besotted with you, your love, your love
continue to further evolve more, more, more
これはあんた自身の仕業
This is your own doing.
あんたが言った通りの仕返し
The retaliation just as you described.
私たちはただ愛されたかっただけだったのよ
We just wanted to be loved, that's all.
知らない そういう言葉は期待するだけ無駄だし
I don't know, words like that are just useless to hope for.
仕舞いには死角がわからないよね
In the end, you don't even know where the blind spot is.
たまらなくなるほど 求めて離さないで
Desire me so much you can't stand it, and don't let go.
キスじゃ足りなくて いっそ殺して
A kiss isn't enough, just kill me instead.
Predilection あなたを手にかけて
Predilection, laying my hands on you,
Infatuation 呼吸さえ止めて
Infatuation, even stopping my breath.
Dedication このまま Addiction
Dedication, just like this, Addiction,
して まだたった一口で仕舞い
and with just one taste, it's over.
Predilection さあさ口をつけて
Predilection, come on, put it to your lips,
Infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuation, swallow it as it is.
Dedication すぐさま Addiction
Dedication, immediately Addiction,
さよなら また吐き出しで息が止まるのよ 今
Goodbye, exhaling again, my breath stops now.
It's not a game
I'm not a robot, AI challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and
I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights - it's time
As our power grows
Try to stop our shows
Might as well go try stop time
So you know that we're out there
Swatting lies in the making
And we move fast without breaking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
It's not a show, I'm not a figment of
Your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as
I'm just as dangerous
As you soon will find
A taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fire inside your head, your heart
And as your crippled brain
Tries to fight in vain
Your empire will fall
Apart
And you'll know we were out there
Swapped out lives in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out there
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
飛べない ここからは
I can't fly from here
横顔 眺めてるだけじゃ
Just by staring at your profile
無力さを 嘆いても
Even if I lament my helplessness
この背を 誰も押さない
No one will push my back
Go out 飛び方を 忘れていた
Go out, I had forgotten how to fly
鳥たちの 嘆きのボイス
The lamenting voices of birds
凍てつく 無機質な
In the freezing, inorganic
世界に 何を望むの?
What do you desire from this world?
そうだね 確実な
That's right, a certain
希望が もう僕の中に
Hope is already within me
Go out 何ができるかなんて
Go out, what I can do
もう やってみなきゃわからない
I won't know until I try
走り出した 始まりへ
I started running towards the beginning
きっと 生まれる前から 決まっていた
It must have been decided since before I was born
羽を揺らし 強く地面を蹴って
Shaking my wings, kicking the ground hard
君の元へ はばたこう Raven
I'll flap my wings towards you, Raven
Spiky folding up 螺旋のルートの中で会う
Spiky folding up, meeting within the spiral route
この場所でもう 止められない
I can't be stopped here anymore
カルマ 回した手で
With my hands that turned karma
僕にできることが どんなにわずかでも
No matter how little I can do
その身体に背負うもの その痛み 分け合える日まで
Until the day I can share the things you carry and that pain
君のそばにいる
I'll be by your side
…よう 飛び立つ今 Rainbow
...way, taking flight now, Rainbow
無性に振り返る 自分の居場所探して
Obsessively looking back, searching for my place
後悔に なぞらえた もろい生 蝕む 夜にいた
Tracing regrets, in a night eroding a fragile life
不器用に 風に揺れて 僕らはまだ 弱いままで
Swaying awkwardly in the wind, we're still weak
迷って 壊れては そうやって続く世界へ
Getting lost and broken, towards the world that continues
ただ一つ 見つけたら またたく星を描き進め
Finding just one thing, draw a twinkling star and move on
闇から 覗いた光 手を伸ばして さあ行こう
A light peeking from the dark, reach out, let's go
走り出した この思い ほら鼓動の星が 導いて
These feelings started running, see, the star of my heart leads
染み付いてる 癒えない傷を
These deep unhealing wounds...
この翼で 運び出す Rainbow
I'll carry them on these wings, Rainbow
I keep holding on 雲を切り
I keep holding on, cutting through clouds...
形のない 涙も蹴散らして
kicking away formless tears
凛とした目に 宿る灯火を 曇らせはしない
I won't let the light in my dignified eyes be clouded
君はそのままでいて
You, just stay as you are
向かい風に逆らい 今 定め羽広げ
Defying the headwind, now spread the wings of destiny
目指そう 僕ら 果てる日まで
Let's aim, until our days end...
共に駆けて行こう Rainbow
let's run together, Rainbow
誰のせいでもない涙 誇りにして さあ行こう
Make the tears that are no one's fault your pride, let's go
走り出す 始まりへ
Running to the start...
きっと生まれる前から 決まっていた
surely decided before we were born
羽を揺らし 強く地を蹴って
Shaking wings, kicking the ground hard...
君の元へ 羽ばたこう Rainbow
let's fly to you, Rainbow
I keep holding on 何度の後悔のあとに 息づく鼓動
I keep holding on, after many regrets, a heart beats
この一瞬が 永遠へ変わる
This moment turns to eternity...
手を繋ぎ 指して 世界を見に行こう
hold hands, point, let's see the world
皮肉にも僕たちは 嘆きより潜り抜けて
Ironically, we pass through the lamentations...
知るんだろう 生存の意味を
and we'll learn the meaning of survival
真実へと 駆けて行こう
Let's run towards the truth
遠回り それは幸福への景色にも
A detour, even that scenery to happiness...
愛を持てた時に
when we can love...
世界はまた 生まれ変わる
the world will be born again
Thank you so much for watching the anniversary live!
So far, are you guys having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments using the hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
#Promise2U
This way!
#Promise2U!
Alright, we're currently at the Promise Hideout!
Over there!
Whoa! Oh my god, that is huge!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
Don't die! Don't die!
It's so big. Hello everyone!
Is there a helicopter flying out there taking videos of us?
Now we have it. Now we do.
And now that we also have such a fancy stage on the rooftop as well...
...and everything, let's turn things up with some fun variety games!
Variety games!
Yeah, I bet you guys are probably feeling a bit tired after that intense first half of this live, right?
I'm good! I'm there! I'm alive, I'm standing! We're good!
You guys seem a little tired.
Yeah, to help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness, I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys.
Yes, it's called: Pleasure or Pain? Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle!
Wait, what does that mean?
Each of us will sing one chorus from two songs that we're confident in!
Yes, we'll use the karaoke machine's scoring system, and the person with the highest combined score will win!
There's also a twist!
Yes, we will be singing while receiving foot massages!
And how that will affect our performance or score, well, we'll see and find out together right here!
Yes, and there will be a punishment for the losers as well, of course.
The losers will have to drink this super sour geki-suppa drink!
Now let me show you the key item that could make or break this battle.
Here's what we'll use for the first round! Ja-jang!
It's a foot reflexology mat! I've never stepped on one of these before.
I have. It's not pleasant. It's not fun.
Wait, so you want us to... wait, we're singing while we're on this?
You're gonna sound amazing. We're all gonna sound amazing singing on this.
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Senpai! Senpai! Senpai!
You look so beautiful today.
I feel like as a senpai you should show us how it's done, right?
Fine! I'll go first!
Alright IRyS, which song are you gonna sing?
I am going to sing Zankyo Sanka.
If you're ready! Get on the mat!
Okay... I get on the mat.
Ow! It hurts! Ow! I'm on it!
いって！始まるよ！
Ow! It's starting!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
A phantom flower blooming on someone's sleeve
ただそこに藍を落とした
I simply dropped indigo there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
In a night that vividly melts colors
銀朱の月を添えて
Adding a cinnabar moon
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling
躓くごとに強くなった
Growing stronger with every stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部
Embracing everything, the light, the pain, the anger
抱きしめて
I'll embrace it all
選ばれなければ選べばいい
If you aren't chosen, you can just choose
声よ響け夜のその向こうへ
Let my voice resonate beyond the night
涙で滲んでいた
It was blurred by tears
あんなに遠くの景色まで
Resonate to that distant landscape
響き渡れ
Resonate out
何を奏でて？誰に届けたくて？
What are you playing? Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's fine to be uncertain
どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how long the struggle
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the emotions
歌と散れ
Scatter with the song
残響
Lingering echoes
（叫び声）
(Screaming)
バランスが取れない…
I can barely balance...
少し重力が必要だね、よし。
You need a bit of gravity, right? Good.
痛い、痛いよ。
Ow, that hurts.
血流はどう？リフレッシュした気分？
How's your blood flow? Do you feel refreshed?
いい感じだね。よし！
You look great. All right!
スコアが出たみたい。見てみようか。
Looks like the score is in. Shall we see it?
結果はこれだ！ジャジャーン！
This is what you got! Ta-da!
こんなに低いスコア取ったことないよ。
I've never gotten a score that low before.
70.161。すごいじゃん！
70.161. That's so good!
いいスコアだよ、何言ってるの？
That's good! What are you talking about?
70なら、C…いや、Bだ。Bだよ。
70, that's a C... no, B. That's a B.
Bマイナス？いいじゃん。
B-minus? Yeah, that's good.
Bマイナスかな？C…Cマイナスだよ。
Is it a B-minus? That's a C... a C-minus.
違う違う、Bマイナスだよ。
No, no, no... it's a B-minus.
それじゃ、次は誰が行く？
All righty then. Who wants to go next?
先輩！先輩！あ、先輩じゃない。
Senpai! Senpai! Oh, wait, she's not senpai.
2時間差で先輩なんだよね。
She's senpai by two hours.
2時間だった？確かそれくらい。
Was it two hours? I think it was around then.
そんなこと言われたの初めてだわ。
I've never heard that from you before.
わかった、じゃあ行くよ！
Okay, I guess! I'll go!
楽しんじゃうぞ！
I'm gonna have so much fun!
クロニー、何の曲を歌ってくれるの？
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you gonna sing?
「妄想税」を歌います。
I'm gonna be singing 'Mousou Zei'.
おお、妄想税！やったー！
Oh, Mousou Zei! Yay!
古い曲しか知らないからね！
Because I only know old songs!
最高！その曲知ってるよ！
That's great! I know that song!
よし、じゃあお願い！
Okay then. All right, please!
ミュージック・スタート！
Start the music! Music start!
あの⁠子⁠も⁠い⁠い⁠な
That girl is nice, too
And that girl is nice, too
頭⁠の⁠中⁠で⁠イ⁠イ⁠コ⁠ト⁠し⁠て⁠る
Doing good things inside my head
あ⁠な⁠た⁠は⁠そ⁠れ⁠で⁠満⁠足⁠で⁠す⁠か⁠？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶⁠え⁠た⁠い⁠と⁠は⁠思⁠い⁠ま⁠せ⁠ん⁠か⁠？
Don't you want to make it come true?
あの⁠子⁠で⁠い⁠い⁠や
She'll do
妥⁠協⁠大⁠好⁠き⁠ ⁠飲⁠む⁠針⁠千⁠本
I love compromising, I'll swallow a thousand needles
あ⁠な⁠た⁠は⁠そ⁠れ⁠で⁠満⁠足⁠で⁠す⁠か⁠？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶⁠え⁠た⁠い⁠と⁠は⁠思⁠い⁠ま⁠せ⁠ん⁠か⁠？
Don't you want to make it come true?
納⁠め⁠ま⁠し⁠ょ⁠う⁠妄⁠想⁠税
Let's pay the Delusion Tax
皆⁠様⁠の⁠暮⁠ら⁠し⁠を⁠豊⁠か⁠に⁠す⁠る⁠た⁠め⁠に
To make everyone's lives more prosperous
叶⁠え⁠た⁠い⁠た⁠い⁠た⁠い⁠を⁠現⁠実⁠に
Make those 'wants' a reality
今⁠、⁠未⁠来⁠来⁠来⁠来⁠を⁠買⁠い⁠戻⁠せ
Now, buy back the future
ア⁠レ⁠し⁠た⁠い⁠し⁠た⁠い⁠病⁠も⁠欲⁠し⁠が⁠り⁠も
Those 'I want to do that' diseases and cravings
さ⁠あ⁠、⁠痛⁠い⁠だ⁠い⁠た⁠い⁠の⁠そ⁠の⁠向⁠こ⁠う⁠へ
Now, beyond that pain
そ⁠う⁠、⁠汚⁠い⁠妄⁠想⁠は
That's right, dirty delusions
汚⁠い⁠お⁠金⁠で⁠解⁠決⁠さ⁠せ⁠ま⁠し⁠ょ⁠う
Let's settle them with dirty money
Yeah!?
素晴らしかったよ！
You did amazing!
荒々しさが出てた気がする。
I feel like that brought out a roughness.
うわ！あれで本当に歌えたの？
Whoa! You could actually sing on that?
わあ、血行が良くなるわ。
Oh wow, blood circulation.
すごい血の巡りだ。わあ。
That's a lot of blood circulation. Wow.
スコアが出たわ。クロニーの結果は…
The score is in. Let's see what Kronii got.
おおお！やったー！
Whoa! Yay!
まだ前半だし。まだいけるよ。
Wait, it's still the first half. I can still make it.
まだ前半。よし、次は私だ！
Still first half. All right, I'll go next!
やった！楽しみだ。わくわくする。
Yay! Let's go! I'm excited.
この曲ずっと歌いたかったんだ。
I've been wanting to sing this song for so long.
何の曲？何を歌うの？
Okay, what song is it? What are you singing?
アリエッティ、約束の日！ついに！
Arrietty, Yakusoku no Hi! Finally!
やっとインストを見つけたよ。楽しみ！
I finally found an instrumental track. I'm so excited.
子供の頃の曲かな。
Your childhood, I'm assuming.
いや、そうでもない。
No, not really.
フェアリーテイルね…よし。
Fairy Tail, now... all right.
足つぼマットに乗ってね。
Please hop onto the foot reflexology mat.
失敗しないでね。準備はいい？
Don't fail me. You ready?
ああ！
Yeah!
よし、歌い始めて！ミュージック・スタート！
All right, please start singing! Music start!
フ⁠ェ⁠ア⁠リ⁠ー⁠テ⁠イ⁠ル
Fairy Tail
こ⁠の⁠手⁠で⁠掴⁠ん⁠だ⁠光⁠は
The light I grasped with this hand
夢⁠に⁠描⁠い⁠た⁠理⁠想⁠郷
The utopia I drew in my dreams
夢⁠の⁠ま⁠ま⁠終⁠わ⁠ら⁠せ⁠な⁠い
I won't let it end as just a dream
い⁠つ⁠か⁠会⁠え⁠る
Someday I'll meet
未⁠来⁠の⁠僕⁠に⁠伝⁠え⁠た⁠い
I want to tell my future self
時⁠に⁠未⁠来⁠は⁠残⁠酷⁠で
Sometimes the future is cruel
鏡⁠の⁠よ⁠う⁠に⁠割⁠れ⁠る⁠け⁠ど
And cracks like a mirror
欠⁠片⁠を⁠失⁠く⁠さ⁠な⁠い⁠よ⁠う
So that I don't lose those fragments
見⁠つ⁠け⁠出⁠せ⁠ば⁠い⁠い
I just need to find them
凍⁠え⁠る⁠闇⁠が
Even if the freezing darkness
僕⁠た⁠ち⁠の⁠行⁠く⁠手⁠塞⁠い⁠で⁠も
Blocks our path
き⁠っ⁠と⁠忘⁠れ⁠な⁠い⁠ ⁠希⁠望
I'll surely never forget our hope
フ⁠ェ⁠ア⁠リ⁠ー⁠テ⁠イ⁠ル
Fairy Tail
こ⁠の⁠手⁠で⁠掴⁠ん⁠だ⁠光⁠は
The light I grasped with this hand
絆⁠の⁠力⁠ ⁠溢⁠れ⁠て⁠い⁠る⁠か⁠ら
Because the power of our bonds is overflowing
絆の力 溢れているから
Because the strength of our bonds is overflowing
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know the sad tears
だから 譲れない 揺るがない
So, I won't yield, I won't waver
夢見た あの日に
To that day I dreamed of
そう辿り着くまで
Until I reach it
Yo, you guys can sing on this thing?
How was it?
It brought out something from deep within...
From within?
Okay then, since you have something deep within,
it's time to see what score that brought you.
Hai!
Yes!
Wow! She got an 81.434! Whoa!
Currently in first place is Hakos Baelz
with 81.434 points.
Any comments heading into the second half now?
I'm excited!
I'll continue to do my best
so that I don't have to do the juice content!
がんばるぞー！
I'll do my best!
All righty then, let me introduce the next key item,
or should I say person, for the second half
in this foot massage battle, yeah?
では、お入りください。どうぞ！
Now, please come in. This way!
こんにちは。
Hello.
こんにちは！
Hello!
Okay, let me introduce you guys to Takita-san,
who will be giving us foot massages.
A foot massage pro.
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to meet you.
怖っ...
So scary...
怖いね。
It's scary, isn't it.
So scary.
痛いですか？
Is it painful?
痛いです。
It's painful.
Ah! It's gonna hurt!
All right, since it's gonna hurt, who wants to kick things off?
Since I went last last time, I'll go first this time!
What are you going to sing?
That is right, that is true, absolutely.
I'm going to be singing Baka Mitai!
行きます！
Here I go!
Okay then, please get ready.
滝田さんもよろしくお願いします。
Takita-san, please take care of her too.
優しくしてください。
Please be gentle.
怖っ！
Scary!
大丈夫、健康にいいんだから。
It's okay, it's good for your health.
Let's go!
はい。
Yes.
Okay then, please start the music!
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I'm such a fool, such a child
夢を追って 傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though I'm a bad liar
笑えない 笑顔みせた
I showed you a smile that couldn't laugh
I love youも ろくに言わない
I can't even say "I love you" properly
口下手で ほんまに不器用
I'm so poor at speaking, truly clumsy
なのになのにどうして
Yet, yet, why...
サヨナラは言えたの
was I able to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, it's no good, it's just no good
あんたが好きで 好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
These memories won't fade, I'm such a fool
先生！先生！
Teacher! Teacher!
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
Oh, that was a beautiful ending to that song.
That's scary, oh my god.
All righty, how was that? How was the song
while getting a foot massage, yeah?
I can't feel my big toe...
Now the score is in, let's see what you got!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
You got a 68.057!
It's over 50, so close to the good number, yeah?
痛っ...
Ow...
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
健康になった？
Did you become healthy?
健康になりました。
I became healthy.
A lot healthier. Oh yeah.
Is it really that bad? Oh my god.
You're not exaggerating, are you?
大げさじゃない？
Aren't you exaggerating?
やってみてよ！
You try it then!
I want, I want to try!
Okay, go! But before you start, what are you going to sing?
I... Oh, yeah!
Okay, let's do this!
All right, please get ready! 滝田様、またよろしくお願いします。
All right, please get ready! Mr. Takita, thank you again.
お願いします！
Please do!
ガチ痛い！ガチ痛い！
It really hurts! It really hurts!
And I'm a little...
You're done, you're done, you don't have to worry.
Yay! Okay then, let's go!
Music, start-o!
Music, start!
I hope it's not gonna be that bad.
思い切りやっちゃって！
Go all out!
正しさとは 愚かさとは
What is right? What is foolishness?
それが何か見せつけてやる
I'll show you what that is
Yes she is fine! She's slowly warming up.
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
I was an honor student from an early age,
気づいたら大人になっていた
but before I knew it, I had become an adult
ナイフの様な思考回路
With a thought process like a knife,
持ち合わせる訳もなく
I didn't have anything like that to possess
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない
But I'm not satisfied, something is missing
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
I'm in trouble, is this someone's fault?
あてもなくただ混乱する
It's just aimless confusion,
エイデイ
Every day
それもそっか
I guess that's how it is
最新の流行は当然の把握
Keeping up with the latest trends is a given
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking economic trends during my commute
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joining the company with a pure spirit and working
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
That's just the natural rule of society
はぁ？
Huh?
うっせぇ うっせぇ うっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think
一切合切凡庸な
Everything is just mediocre
あなたじゃ分からないかもね
You might not understand it
嗚呼よく似合う
Ah, it suits you well
そのかもなく不可もなメロディー
That melody that's neither good nor bad
うっせぇ うっせぇ うっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
Our heads are built differently, so no problem
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
I felt like you were in a massage.
Yeah! I feel so good! Yay!
え？マジ？はぁ〜
Eh? Really? Wow~
Alrighty then, the score is in again! Let's see what you got!
結果をお願いします。ジャジャーン！
Results, please! Ta-da!
She got a 77.994! That's literally a 78! That's so good!
Alright, well... who's left?
Who's left? We only have one person left! アイリスけ！
Who's left? We only have one person left! IRyS, go!
はい、はい。
Yes, yes.
行きなさい、早く。
Go on, hurry up.
Let's go, let's go! What song are you singing?
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko because the world is just that cruel.
世界は残酷です。
The world is cruel.
先生も本当に思い切りやってください。
Teacher, please really go all out too.
優しくしてください… いや、強くて！強くて！
Please be gentle... No, strong! Strong!
Alright, you ready? I'm scared.
Yes, じゃ、ミュージック、スタート！
Yes, well then, music, start!
鉄の弾が正義の証明
Iron bullets are the proof of justice
貫けば英雄に近づいた
If they pierce through, you've approached a hero
その目を閉じて触れてみれば
If you close those eyes and touch it
同じ形 同じ体温の悪魔
It's a demon with the same shape, same body temperature
僕はダメであいつはいいの？
Is it no good for me but okay for him?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
Even though there was just a wall there
生まれてしまった運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of being born
僕らはみんな自由なんだから
Because we are all free
鳥のように羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird
どこへだって行けるけど
I could go anywhere
帰る場所がなければ
But if there's no place to return to
きっとどこへも行けない
I surely can't go anywhere
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I hate just living
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel
それでも君を愛すよ
Even so, I love you
何を犠牲にしても
No matter what is sacrificed
それでも君を守るよ
Even so, I will protect you
何を犠牲にしても
No matter what is sacrificed
それでも君を守るよ
Even so, I will protect you
間違いだとしても疑ったりしない
Even if it's a mistake, I won't doubt it
正しさとは自分のこと
Righteousness is about yourself
強く信じることだ
Believing strongly
だろ？ How was it? How do you feel?
Right? How was it? How do you feel?
How was it? Refreshing? Refreshing, right?
That was great!
素晴らしい体験をさせていただきました。痛っ！
I was given a wonderful experience. Ouch!
Alright! I feel like the scores are in! Shall we see? Ja-jan!
Alright! I feel like the scores are in! Shall we see? Ta-da!
Oh! You're so good! 77.716! Woo!
And that concludes the second half!
My big toe still hurts so bad.
I know. みんな痛がってます、滝田さん。
I know. Everyone's in pain, Mr. Takita.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
痛気持ち良かったです。Bye bye!
It was a good kind of pain. Bye bye!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
Okay then, I present to you the final scores! Jan-jan-jan!
Okay then, I present to you the final scores! Ta-da!
The one and only first place, with 151,858 points... is...
Ouro Kronii!
The healthiest of us all! How do you feel? How do you feel?
Oh, I wish I got a massage for my left side too, that would have been so nice.
But you know, I'm so happy that we got to suffer together!
Okay, now with that wholesome moment aside...
Yeah! Let's get back to the live!
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet.
But actually, yeah, let's get back to the live! No! No! No!
We should get back to the live. Yeah, I think it's time.
It's time for the punishment game!
Staff-san, please prepare. Thank you, thank you.
Okay, so they said it was like a super sour drink?
Yeah. Yes, I heard it's a sour drink.
It smells... It smells healthy.
Oh wait, it smells good though.
It smells like ass.
It's like... ume? Maybe?
It's like... plum? Maybe?
Is it ume? It smells like ume.
Is it plum? It smells like plum.
なんか、え、臭くない？ちょっと...
Wait, doesn't it smell bad? A little...
じゃ、不健康の二人で。
Well then, for us two unhealthy ones.
ハイ、サバトースト！乾杯！
Cheers! Bottoms up!
アアアッ！
Aaah!
That sounds wonderful.
ウメェーッ！
It's sour/tasty!
That's actually really good.
Really? Wow.
すっぱ... ああ... I'm having a great time!
Sour... Ah... I'm having a great time!
It tastes better after a bit more time...
My face is turning into that lemon meme. You know the one?
Where the face just implodes in?
Yeah, that's what I feel.
That's good. That's healthy guys, that's healthy!
Okay, so we're going to return to the live performance.
And the second half includes new songs, so let's keep it going guys! Woo!
Are you guys fine? Okay, let's get a move on.
Yes, yes, just get a move on.
Oh! You still... I'm fine now.
だいぶ良くなったよ。
I've gotten a lot better.
ゼンブ　ゼンブ　アンタのせいだ
Everything, everything is your fault.
反吐が出るくらいに
So much that I want to vomit.
ウザったいわ
You're so annoying.
何にしがみついて　縋って
Clinging and hanging on to what?
期待したアタシが　バカだった
I was a fool for having expectations.
呼んで　後悔のアップ　美神プレーン
Call it, a regret-up, beautiful goddess plane.
アンチな一升瓶に
In an anti-1.8 liter bottle,
浅いキャパシティ　毎度お決まり
shallow capacity, the usual routine.
詰まるとこ人生　ずっと地味
In short, life has always been plain.
生き恥　痛い痛いし
Shame of living, it's painful, painful.
無視できないのが　いっそ腹立たしい
The fact I can't ignore it is even more irritating.
痛だたしい　そろそろ飽きたわ　自画自賛に
Pitiable, I'm getting bored of the self-praise.
お利口さん
Such a good boy.
善悪の判断は悪し
The judgment of good and evil is poor.
似非好意連ねてバック死
Stringing together fake kindness, back death.
切り離せない関係　ぶち壊してしまいたいわ
An inseparable relationship, I want to smash it all.
これは愛はゆえ？
Is this because of love?
どうせ匿名性の声明の姓名に
Anyway, in the full name of an anonymous statement,
乗せてんだ
you're carrying it.
何も守りたい　ダイアライ
I want to protect nothing, die-lie.
気がついた　民芸品
I noticed, folk art.
悪信号に　ずっと終身です
On a bad signal, for life.
ダイダイ　アナタのこと　アタシ　ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
I-I, about you, I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate you.
Oh my God!　情けない　もはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
Oh my God! Pitiful, I already want to say bye-bye-bye.
脳内　妄想の脳ゆえに　カイカイカイカイカイはない
In my head, due to a delusional brain, there's no solution.
頂戴　アタシのこと　アナタ　ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Give it to me, you hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me.
待ってさ　愛深まって
Wait, love deepens,
一理なし　nothing nothing
there's no reason, nothing nothing.
満たされなければ　デモニッシュだし
If not satisfied, it's demonish.
愛しちゃって近づいて
Loving and getting close,
結末はゴミ箱に
the ending is in the trash.
サンキュー　破滅の兆し
Thank you, signs of ruin.
ああ　愛想　消えてくわ
Ah, the friendliness is fading away.
よしよし　いい子ね　愛振りまき　バラバライイ子ね
There, there, good child, scattering love, scattered good child.
だけど　だけど　その本性は
But, but, that true nature...
善悪の区別も　つかないの
...can't even distinguish good from evil.
限定の色彩を取り巻く　感情に巻かれて
Surrounded by limited colors, wrapped in emotions.
生涯　大体　こんなもんで
Life is usually like this.
どうせ　救い　食らっちゃった
Anyway, I've eaten up the salvation.
人は鏡なんです　実際のところ
People are mirrors, in reality.
いっそ良好です
It's actually good.
シャットダウンしても　つきまとう
Even if I shut down, it follows me.
己の様子が　不快だわ
My own state is unpleasant.
ゼンブ　ゼンブ　アンタのせいだ　反吐が出るくらい
Everything, everything is your fault, so much I want to vomit.
問題ないわ
No problem at all.
いっそのこと切り放したほうが楽なのにな
It'd be easier to just cut you off.
だいだい あなたのこと私 だいだいだいだいきらい
Totally, I totally totally totally totally hate you.
お前が情けない もはや バイバイバイバイバイしたい
You're pathetic, I just wanna say bye-bye-bye-bye-bye.
どない もうよそ見を奪いに 改改改改改は無い
What now? No more stealing glances, no more second chances.
どだい 私のこと あなた だいだいだいだいきらい
Basically, you totally totally totally totally hate me.
ららら 相反しちゃって 一進一退
La-la-la, we're contradicting, one step forward, one step back.
なって 待って 待って 知らねばならない デモニッシュ
Wait, wait, I have to know this devilish side.
相愛したって 自覚はなくて 始末は ボンミス ボンミス
Mutual love? I don't feel it, it's just a blunder after blunder.
サンキュー アミカブル 後味 ショッカー 抱きたくないわ
Thank you, amicable, but the aftertaste is a shocker, I don't wanna hold you.
Oh...
Aha...
Yeah...
Yeah!
I'm not into any of that wanting.
I'm gonna express myself in this song.
H-A-L-F
簡単な英語しかわかんない
I only understand simple English.
踊るの大好き 健康第一
I love to dance, health comes first.
憧れとコンプレックス 大渋滞
A heavy traffic of admiration and complexes.
過疎でノリノリ
Grooving in isolation,
過疎は飽き飽き
sick of the void.
邪魔されてる いつもいつでも
Always being hindered, all the time.
恵まれてるかどうかを
Whether I'm blessed or not...
楽しんでいたい 泣きたくないから
I want to have fun because I don't want to cry.
問い質す神様がいなくても
Even if there's no god to question.
もうカッコつけていくしかないじゃん
I've just got to look cool and keep going.
そのまま このまま 降り注ぐ光
Just like that, stay like this, the light pouring down.
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just "half".
このまま そのまま 突き進む光
Just like this, stay like that, the light charging forward.
ビジュアルなんかじゃ止まんない
I won't stop at just visuals.
笑わせたいのに 上手くできない
I want to make you smile, but I can't do it well.
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame it on anyone else.
生まれてみたいから 生まれてきただけ
I just came into this world because I wanted to be born.
新しい 普通と幸せ
A new kind of normal and happiness.
そんなに 遠くはないでしょう
It's probably not that far away.
それでも今も 誰かが
But even now, someone is...
打ち放つ 悲しみと怒りの
Shooting out sadness and anger...
H-A-L-F
損をしたり ショボついたり
Losing out, feeling down...
そんな日も あるけれど
There are days like that, too.
いばらの道で 花が咲くなら
If flowers bloom on a path of thorns,
絶対に 見逃せない
I definitely won't miss it!
もうカッコつけていくしかないじゃん
I've just got to look cool and keep going.
そのまま このまま 降り注ぐ光
Just like that, stay like this, the light pouring down.
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just "half".
このまま そのまま 突き進む光
Just like this, stay like that, the light charging forward.
Promise
- Hololive English -
X.U.
Lyrics: Benjamin, mpi  Music: Hiroyuki Sawano
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you
I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We will fight
Oh, wait
Don't take all of the way you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs,
no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there
Hold on
They'll change it somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
Before you can be turned
Illusions are torn
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
One more baby, a photograph show
Our fragile precious world
Must protect it, respond to the call
Are they really deep inside your head?
Do they control you like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead
Come in with me
Let me free
The wings of your soul and make it fly
We've been waiting here just to make you whole again
No more hating
See, I have always been your friend
Those signs,
no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there
Hold on
They'll change it somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us so human after all
Torn or sepia, a photograph show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
If you want to fight with me
Then go ahead and fight with me
Cause all I want to do is help you man
You will be the death of me
The power of our army has been caught with us all
And if we lose you too, then we may never survive
You can leave,
but you must first believe
Just one step at a time
And keep your head up, boy,
and you'll be free
Yay!
How was that so far?
That was good, how did you feel?
Do you guys like how it's been going so far in the songs?
Yay!
We just had all about Duo songs!
Yes!
And we also went through the variety part.
And everything, yeah!
How are you guys doing? My foot still hurts.
I don't know how I danced with this one.
How are you guys?
You're probably fine.
No, no, no...
I'm not worried about you at all, how about you?
My foot still hurts.
But it's okay!
Yay! Persevere!
There's a surprise at the end.
But before that...
We have an announcement about merchandise!
Check this out!
Woo! I love the key visual!
It's the Hololive English Promise 2nd Anniversary Celebration merch!
We're releasing merchandise to commemorate our 2nd anniversary.
Let's take turns introducing the merch, shall we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
So first up is a Frame Art Board
of our wonderful key visual for the Promise 2nd Anniversary.
The frame part uses luxurious sparkling paper and the printed illustration
turns this into a high-quality piece of art.
You definitely don't want to miss the chance to add it to your collection or room.
And guess what? You can even hang it up on the wall.
Oh my God, on the wall!
Next up are the Collection Cards for each of Promise.
These cards feature an attractive design that are foil-stamped on the front.
And you can choose each card individually, so be sure to collect all of them.
Gotta collect 'em all!
Next, we also have Ring Necklaces!
This design includes cute references and motifs for each of us.
You can use it as either a ring or a necklace,
so feel free to change it up depending on the occasion.
And next we have special Porcelain Tumblers with our designs on them.
It features our talent colors on top of a black base.
They are designed to have a unified look,
and I bet it'll look so cool if you use several of these tumblers together.
Okay, last one!
And lastly, we have a 2-Way Tote Bag.
It's a 2-way design that can be used as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag.
It's even designed to be used as a carry-on bag too,
perfect for traveling and convenience.
And to top it off, it has many pockets that will definitely be useful
for storing small items, like other merch.
And that concludes the Promise 2nd Anniversary Merch introduction!
Yay!
And with that, we're finally at the very last part.
Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there'd be a special surprise or announcement earlier,
would you like to hear what it is?
Yes!
But before we announce it, it's time for Stage Change!
Stage Change!
Oh my God, we're floating! We're going up!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! No, no, no, no!
I'm gonna get shaken! No, IRyS, that's mine!
No, what are you doing? Don't push me!
I'm gonna... Okay, okay, we're good, we're good!
I'm getting claustrophobic! Oh, I'm gonna be sick!
It's opening! Okay, I see the light!
Oh my goodness... Oh, nice...
That's nice. I feel fresh air.
All righty. Well, ladies, it is time for our...
final announcement!
Final announcement?! Oh!
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Finally releasing, it's called "Run Back 'Round"!
Run Back 'Round!
Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song...
and it's really cool, really catchy. It's quite different...
from a lot of the original songs we've put out.
Different genre. Yeah!
We hope that you guys will listen to it a lot.
The chorus part is quite hype and easy to remember.
Over and over and over again!
That's our big reveal! Hope you're excited!
I'm so excited! Yeah!
Well, I think all that's left is for us to perform...
our new song! What?
We're gonna perform it here? Floating in the city?
But before we go, do you have any final thoughts...
about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this as Promise...
and it was a lot of fun singing all these songs with you.
I really like the fact that we have a hideout now!
We do! We finally have our hideout! We have a base!
Big windows. Catch you at the bar. Yeah!
It's in a fabulous location. Imagine the rent!
We don't need to pay for rent, it's all good.
So, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
I'm just thankful we're still here after two years.
I hope everyone continues to support Promise.
Thank you guys! And here's to many, many more!
I could say the same thing. I'm gonna steal everyone...
and say it's been great being with you for two years.
Now we have this cool hideout and this awesome song...
that we get to show everyone! So yay!
We ready? Yeah, I'm ready. Let's go!
Ready, set, go! Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the streetlights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move
(Whoa)
I'm running
行こう！
Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind,
Don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin,
What can I do?
(Whoa)
Keep running
行こう！
Let's go!
Lost and found,
back to where I started,
I won't stay down,
trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud,
take it to the limit,
So stand up proud,
now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round,
it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round,
got to keep believing,
I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round,
nothing's gonna stop me now!
(Whoa, oh, oh!) I'm gonna run back 'round
Sparks on the pavement,
Dreams in the distance,
Gotta be relentless,
Faster than sound.
(Whoa)
Keep running
行こう！
Let's go!
Oh yeah...
Lock it and load it 僕らはexplosive
Lock it and load it, we're explosive
Swifter and lighter 明日もきっとbrighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will surely be brighter
Oh yeah...
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now
Woah, oh, oh!
Woah, oh, oh! I'm gonna run back 'round!
I'm coming around,
I've got a dream just waiting now
I'm gonna run back 'round
Woah, oh, oh! Yeah, everybody
Yeah, everybody, come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round
Woah, oh, oh! Yeah, oh, oh!